{ "backgroundcolor":"#000000",
 "height":33,
 "infinite":false,
 "layers":[
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJztm0uOwjAQBb2bA3H7WTLXyY4LIKSxFFn+pRO7X0wtakUC5U6RjxBbCGEDWIBXg1Gfkb7uPYcZsxwx2290s\/pa3vc5eRY5no31XjG\/1jwVjsVZv5k9jka1S7Bx9x7pcl16m\/wRRqVL7znckd4uS+cjZbyb3LcJx2l1WWvS+5iXGvD2wOsaryNdPoTX8\/ePtwde54h9fVqjS7xUyHWZ244u8ZoJXeKl6NVzHd8CXeI1l94ut0CXeM2j1GXtnEmXeI2GLvFS9KJLvBS9ervkuQevmfA8jpei19nfex4Ca4j8Jnj74GUj7evuXX584vdf6VyO1zFKXabb0SVeM6FLvBS96BIvRS\/uL\/FS9LJ2+QqaXab\/EfH2wcvGvstce\/tta23CGnj3GKk12XOfGa\/psAYKbeau3a0uS23CGqh02fIs7es9P\/jeLmv79q5Tqecjs1H1o0v7nEYe\/9kzuqqxUf7WWXnP1bo+bx+AFm93ap6I",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":33,
         "name":"back",
         "opacity":0.5,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":166,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "compression":"zlib",
         "data":"eJztm0sOgyAURZl1Qd1g1+WwW+oGGgcmhii8BwIXPSe5o\/6uj1MjsQ0B4B78Mmn1GfHjdyA3yxazfWK30r4l7\/utPbgLWDvkvj9XJ0ZhLWr7WWkxz6uj6iUpS4rR3fDy2TniaN3XvESj4uXoOcyWzSuLl2dOKkeF0XOYOSkvU06qQS8f6r1iN\/fgZT308lHi5TvoH48a9PKx9Vpds+558NIPvXzgZR\/o5ePIy9x+HC\/90MuH1csQ8LIGevk48zJ1zsRLP\/TygZd9oJcPvOwDvXxYvWTfUwe9fLAf7wO9fFi8TN3veXdrmmcJ4bPP6D4bSxQVVHvFfs3uJdyDMy9j8BJ6gpegCF6CIqXXl9+Al9COvZee31+qehn\/T0QFevlIeelxk9wjKqSctFxn7s+ZZP4ouJlz8sjLkHgumT8qXuZ6njF6fuS5XqawHmfp61rEg2o\/vLTRe\/17c5VjrfqXzmr0XK3M0hNg4w+0nuOu",
         "encoding":"base64",
         "height":33,
         "name":"front",
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"tilelayer",
         "visible":true,
         "width":166,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#5555ff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"mods",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":712,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedrustypanel",
                     "front":"slopedrustypanel"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":48
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":713,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":256,
                 "x":384,
                 "y":40
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":714,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":735,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":648,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":758,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":759,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":376,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":760,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":761,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":765,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":64,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":768,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":952,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":772,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":368,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":774,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":344,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":779,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":680,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":784,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":976,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":786,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":672,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":96,
                 "id":789,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":1256,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":794,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":256,
                 "x":992,
                 "y":216
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":795,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"castlewalls1",
                     "front":"castlewalls1"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":984,
                 "y":56
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":797,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"darksmoothstone",
                     "front":"darksmoothstone"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":984,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "height":8,
                 "id":798,
                 "name":"",
                 "properties":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"true",
                     "back":"slopedrustypanel",
                     "front":"slopedrustypanel"
                    },
                 "propertytypes":
                    {
                     "allowOverdrawing":"string",
                     "back":"string",
                     "front":"string"
                    },
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":272,
                 "x":984,
                 "y":208
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"objects",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "gid":5877,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":800,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":336,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":5877,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":801,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":640,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":5877,
                 "height":40,
                 "id":802,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":48,
                 "x":944,
                 "y":200
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ffff00",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"wiring - lights & guns",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#ff0000",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"monsters & npcs",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "color":"#00ffff",
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"wiring - locked door",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"outside the map",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"anchors etc",
         "objects":[
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":755,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":72,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":756,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":984,
                 "y":168
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":757,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":944,
                 "y":200
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":248,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":770,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":1248,
                 "y":168
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":247,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":793,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":512,
                 "y":16
                }, 
                {
                 "gid":247,
                 "height":8,
                 "id":799,
                 "name":"",
                 "rotation":0,
                 "type":"",
                 "visible":true,
                 "width":8,
                 "x":1120,
                 "y":256
                }],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }, 
        {
         "draworder":"topdown",
         "name":"items",
         "objects":[],
         "opacity":1,
         "type":"objectgroup",
         "visible":true,
         "x":0,
         "y":0
        }],
 "nextobjectid":803,
 "orientation":"orthogonal",
 "renderorder":"right-down",
 "tiledversion":"1.1.6",
 "tileheight":8,
 "tilesets":[
        {
         "firstgid":1,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/materials.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":198,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/supports.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":235,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/miscellaneous.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":259,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/liquids.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":287,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/ancient.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":450,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/apex.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":821,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/avian.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":1126,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/floran.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":1321,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/generic.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3305,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/glitch.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3531,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/human.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":3819,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/hylotl.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4051,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-race\/novakid.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4115,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/breakable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":4425,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/decorative.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5866,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/door.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":5998,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/farmable.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6073,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/furniture.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6427,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/light.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6885,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/railpoint.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6890,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/teleporter.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":6932,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/trap.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7136,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-category\/wire.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7358,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/container.json"
        }, 
        {
         "firstgid":7643,
         "source":"..\/..\/..\/tilesets\/packed\/objects-by-type\/teleporter.json"
        }],
 "tilewidth":8,
 "type":"map",
 "version":1,
 "width":166
}